export const QuestionsData = [
  {
    index: "collapseOne",
    question: " how to send money online ?",
    ans: " Venmo: Best rated for mobile. Cash app: Best for referral bonus. Zelle: Fastest for domestic transfers (tie with Google Pay). Google Pay: Fastest for domestic transfers (tie with Zelle). PayPal: Most popular online. Walmart2Walmart: Best for nonbank transfers.",
  },
  {
    index: "collapseTow",
    question: " Are money transfer apps safe ?",
    ans: "Money transfer apps are safe, but they're not foolproof. If you've ever texted or called the wrong number, that mistake could cost you when sending money. It's important to understand that you may not get that money back. In most cases, providers won't help if the recipient refuses to return the misdirected funds.",
  },
  {
    index: "collapseThree",
    question: " How much are money transfer fees ?",
    ans: "Up to $35 per transfer for domestic transfers. Up to $50 per transfer for international transfers. Up to $25 per transfer for domestic transfers. Up to $35 per transfer for international transfers. Up to 3% of the amount in foreign currency.",
  },
  {
    index: "collapseFour",
    question: " How much money can I send ?",
    ans: "There will be no limit for Cash Deposit and Fund Transfer. · For Cash Withdrawal, transaction limit will be Tk.10,00,000 per day per account. Maximum Online Charge: Tk. 1,500.00 Upto Tk. 20,000.00: Tk. 15.00 Above Tk. 20,000.00: Tk. 15.00 + 0.20 for next ...",
  },
  {
    index: "collapseFive",
    question: " What is the fastest way to send money abroad ?",
    ans: "Using your debit or credit card is generally the fastest way to pay for an international money transfer, with bank transfers coming in a close second. As a rule of thumb, using cash to pay for your transfer is the slowest method of the three.",
  },
  {
    index: "collapseSix",
    question: " Which currency can i send ?",
    ans: "You can send money to and from these currencies AED — Emirati Dirham Within the UAE. AUD — Australian dollar Within Australia. BGN — Bulgarian lev Within Bu ...",
  },
  {
    index: "collapseSeven",
    question: " How to use Online Bank BD ?",
    ans: "Our Online Banking service allows you to bank from anywhere, anytime with total security and confidentiality. And it's absolutely free! Fresh Online Banking · Register Online Banking with... · View Transaction History",
  },
  {
    index: "collapseEight",
    question: " Cancel transaction",
    ans: "If you want to eliminate the transaction before then, contact the merchant who placed the charge. Ask them to contact your card issuer and reverse the ...",
  },
  {
    index: "collapseNine",
    question: " How does Online Bank BD protect your money ?",
    ans: " This service will facilitate you to transfer fund from your IBBL accounts to other IBBL accounts instantly. In this case your source IBBL accounts should be ...",
  },
  {
    index: "collapseTen",
    question: " Can I send multiple payments ?",
    ans: "Generally, multiple wires can only come from one source. · If funds come from multiple sources, the additional sources will need to complete identity",
  },
];
